<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>picklejuice</title><link>https://picklejuicedev.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on picklejuice</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://picklejuicedev.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Converting a Kaggle notebook to a Kedro Pipeline</title><link>https://picklejuicedev.github.io/posts/notebook_2_kedro/</link><pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://picklejuicedev.github.io/posts/notebook_2_kedro/</guid><description>&lt;p>This tutorial is aimed at Data Scientists who want to convert Jupyter Notebook to a Kedro pipeline. Notebooks are a great way to experiment and explore data, figure out what machine learning model works well and illustrate outcomes. But it is very hard to maintain notebooks, they don&amp;rsquo;t play nice with repositories, testing can&amp;rsquo;t be automated and you can&amp;rsquo;t reuse code from them or integrate them into a bigger workflow. So Kedro takes all these good things we have learned from software engineering and applies them to data science projects. But how to get started?&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Setting up a Virtual Environment and VS Code for Kedro</title><link>https://picklejuicedev.github.io/posts/quick_kedro_setup/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://picklejuicedev.github.io/posts/quick_kedro_setup/</guid><description>&lt;p>Utilising best software engineering practice with Kedro starts with setting up a virtual environment and an IDE to work with.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This short guide shows you how to get started with Python&amp;rsquo;s built in venv environment manager together with VS Code to have a Kedro project set up in no time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I am assuming you have Python 3.7 or greater and &lt;a href="https://code.visualstudio.com/">VS Code&lt;/a> installed. I am using Windows for the prompt examples, for macs/linux replace &lt;code>python&lt;/code> with &lt;code>python3&lt;/code> most other commands should be pretty similar - your prompt will look a bit different too. For some distributions you may also need to install venv separatly.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Tools Infrastructure for Production</title><link>https://picklejuicedev.github.io/posts/tools_overview/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://picklejuicedev.github.io/posts/tools_overview/</guid><description>&lt;p>Working in a team on a project that will span several months or years, you will need to create an infrastructure to support your team as the codebase grows. In this article I will discuss a bunch of tools, what they do and why you would need them. Every project, team and business is different though, so this is part of my experience and you will need to tweak the selection of tools and their priorities to your own use-case.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://picklejuicedev.github.io/aboutme/</link><pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2022 14:07:09 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://picklejuicedev.github.io/aboutme/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="sean-westgate">Sean Westgate&lt;/h2>

&lt;figure >
 
 &lt;img src="https://picklejuicedev.github.io/images/sean_portrait.jpg" 
 
 width="220" 
 />
 
 
&lt;/figure>

&lt;p>I am an entrepreneurial technologist with over 20 years&amp;rsquo; experience driving innovation, building products, running teams and growing businesses. I am working as a Technical Consultant helping tech teams improve and deliver disruptive products. Please check out my &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/sean-westgate-88362045/">LinkedIn&lt;/a> profile for a full list of experiences, or keep on reading to find out more about me.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As the driving founder of &lt;a href="https://www.green-hippo.com/">Green Hippo Ltd&lt;/a>, I took the company all the way from a tiny office in North London to a successful international business with worldwide distribution. Our market leading product, the Hippotizer, served up video on many high profile shows, including the &lt;a href="https://www.green-hippo.com/green-hippo-2017-eurovision-song-contest-performance-wows-massive-global-audience/">Eurovision Song Contest&lt;/a>, &lt;a href="https://www.green-hippo.com/superbowllady-gaga/">Lady Gaga at the Super Bowl Half-time Show&lt;/a> and the &lt;a href="https://www.green-hippo.com/88th-academy-awardsthe-oscars/">&amp;ldquo;Oscars&amp;rdquo; - Academy Award&lt;/a> amongst many others.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>